JESSICA PATEL

30 St. Andrew St, London, ON N6H 1Z6 +1-(519)-319-3480 | jpate272@uwo.ca | Website | LinkedIn

Summary

Recent Computer Science Graduate from Western University. Hold professional work experience of two years in software industry. Sound command over programming languages. Innovative, versatile, goal oriented, excellent technical and soft skills and fluent in verbal and written communication.

Work experience

Western University 09/2018- 04/2019

Graduate Teaching Assistant

- Held lab sessions for the second-year undergraduate course, Software tools and Systems Programming, comprising C language and shell scripting.
- Conducted tutorials, held office hours, graded assignments, proctored examinations for the course during Fall and Winter terms.

IBM India Pvt. Ltd. 07/2016- 06/2018

Service Delivery Specialist

- Worked for the client account, ABN AMRO (Netherlands based bank).
- Worked on the VuGen Scripts, HP BAC 8.06, HP BSM, HP Load Runner, Heliview and Service now
- Focused on scripting and running tests on applications to analyze it under load and maintain system health
- Gratifying client-side issues in the form of Incidents, problems and tasks, resolving them with technical expertise and expediting correction or adjustment and following up to ensure resolution.
- Documenting the major problems, coming up with innovative automated scripts to fasten the work

Education

Western University 09/2018- 12/2019

Master of Science (Computer Science)
G. H. Raisoni College of Engineering

Bachelor of Engineering (Information technology)

06/2012-06/2016

Technical Skills

Programming Languages – Java, Python, C, JavaScript **Web Technologies** – XML, HTML, CSS **Database** – MySQL, Oracle, MongoDB **Version Control** – GIT

Academic Projects

Image Classification (Python | Jupyter Notebook | Pandas | Matplotlib | NumPy | TensorFlow | Sklearn | Keras)
 E-commerce Customer Churn Model (Python | Jupyter Notebook | Pandas | Matplotlib)
 Predicting weather forecast (Python | Jupyter Notebook | Apache Spark | AngularJS | MongoDB | Object Storage)
 5 Layer Security Architecture for Connected Vehicle System